I can't deny that much how's it shaped
me never quite sure of where they should
place me I was once a baby always crazy
maybe foaming booming rabies to wit
nights I would drop the Sun came up I
was young of a smart but slow dumbest
truck I've got known for much I'm here
to press my luck if y'all still got
dreams then can you hold them up we were
born to smile that we are going to drown
if you could lift me up thinking you
hold me down on the summer nights
if you come back here in a new
now back to the magic that made me
what's top of the ladder your weight
class and really like weight classes
place faster pace to my place of
all of the grates past I found the
world's on the
so maybe it's just you that I don't
respect and now I
to be the dopest ever I was nobody but I
was a little bit kind of the Whomper to
let her hit a cereal drop I told you it
is good to be gettin that cooperative
kool-aid for two bucks yet Mike walked
over ty one day
stop
you